女士们先生们...
Ladies and gentlemen...
据本国法律规定 婚姻...
marriage,according to the law of this country...
是一个男人与一个女人...
is the union of one man with one woman...
共同生活的一种自由结合...
voluntarily entered into for life...
其他人是不能干涉的
to the exclusion of all others.
- 迈克这位是... - 这里在做什么?
- Mickey here is... - What's going on here?
这里以上帝之名在做些什么?
What in God's name is happening here?
那是我妻子
That is my wife!
- 我喜欢你这套西装 - 你上周已经嫁给我了
- I love the suit. - You married us last week.
本作品由Norm HALFCD Team倾情奉献\N感谢原作提供资源.仅供学习交流.严禁用于商业行为\N请自觉于下载后24小时内删除!如果喜欢本片,请购买正版!
更多精彩 尽在www.NormTeam.com
压制:鬼谷子  字幕:鬼谷子\NCompression:GV-Sir  Subtitles:GV-Sir
飞天大盗 第1季第5集
S01E05 A Touch of Class
你喜欢看我穿着婚纱 是吗?
You enjoy seeing me in a wedding dress,don't you?
有一点点
Just a little bit.
(西班牙囚徒:通过取得人们信任的诈骗手段)
西班牙囚徒怎样?我们有好几年没做这个了
What about a Spanish Prisoner?We haven't done one of them in years.
首先我们能一直生活在一起 看看它是怎么做的
We could always live together first,see how it goes.
我们请到了很多的婚礼嘉宾 不是吗?
We've got enough toasters,ain't we?
我讨厌每周都结婚
I'm sick of getting married every week.
- 下次换个角色 - Leighton Buzzard（诈骗手法）如何?
- Next time,it can be someone else. - What about a Leighton Buzzard?
好啊 那很有趣
Well,that was fun.
我从1972年后就没干过了
I haven't run like that since 1972.
- 我们搞砸了,迈克 - 是的
- We screwed up,Michael. - Yes,we did.
我昨天和一个人谈了关于马的事
I talked to a man about a horse yesterday.
- 别 Albert - 不 Albie
- No,Albert. - No,Albie.
迈克 我们现在做什么?
What do we do now,Mickey?
我们保持冷静相信自己的才能
We keep calm and trust our talent.
向受惊者敬酒
Libation for a shocked body.
那是谁?
Who's that?
你直瞪瞪看着的那人是谁?
The woman you're gawping at,who is she?
她是"凯瑟琳・温特波夫人"
She is "Mrs.Katherine Winterborn...
最近与商人斯蒂文・温特波离婚
"recently divorced from Stephen Winterborn,businessman.
她否认因赌气而杀了他的狗"
"She denied killing his dog in a fit of pique."
她杀了那小子的狗?
She killed the bloke's dog?
"离婚后 她带她丈夫去洗衣店...
"In the ensuing divorce,she took her husband to the cleaners...
把他们的旅馆和温泉疗养旅馆原封不动地留给了他...
"leaving him the bare bones of their hotel and spa business...
还有一只空的狗篮"
"and an empty dog basket."
我在想什么 Albert?
What am I thinking,Albert?
你在想使用康格里夫(诈骗手法)
You're thinking about doing the Congreve.
的确是
I am indeed.
- 什么是康格里夫? - 威廉・康格里夫 剧作家
- What's the Congreve? - William Congreve.Playwright.
天堂不像由爱转恨一样狂暴
"Heaven has no rage like love to hatred turned
地狱也不像个轻蔑的女人一样暴怒
"Nor hell a fury like a woman scorned"
我们去缝合一颗复仇的女人心
We're going to stitch up a vengeful woman.
好的 Danny Stacie 订住Winterborn的伦敦温泉旅馆...
Okay.Danny,Stacie, book into Winterborn's London spa...
看你能从Katherine的前职员那里得到些什么信息
and see what information you can get out of Katherine's former staff.
Katherine Winterborn
Katherine Winterborn emerged triumphant...
从最近与Stephen Winterborn离婚的痛苦进程里获利...
from recent bitter divorce proceedings against Stephen Winterborn...
她设法维持Winterborn温泉连锁旅馆单独管理...
Who managed to maintain sole control of the Winterborn chain of spa hotels...
而Stephen正打算让股票上市
which Stephen is about to float on the stock exchange.
Daniel 你打听到什么?
Daniel,what did you learn?
好的 我和一个治疗学家谈过 她是个甜心
Well,I spoke to one of the therapists.Very sweet girl.
在我们国家 水不会这样暖和的
In my country,the water wouldn't be so warm.
Winterborn夫人非常强调纪律
Mrs.Winterborn was a stickler for discipline.
她喜欢严格,孤僻,残酷的作风
Strict.Aloof.Cruel when she felt like it.
员工帽子掉了也会被解雇
Sacked staff at the drop of a hat.
却很擅长于经营
But very good at her business.
还有什么?Stacie
Stacie?Anything else?
她与丈夫的关系非常不稳定
She had a very volatile relationship with her husband.
有一天她把他所有的西装都扯碎了
One day she cut up all his suits
而他把她所有的绘画都撕破以报复她
and he retaliated by ripping up all her drawings.
他们曾去划船 他因一个商务旅行而离开了...
They had a row.He went away on a business trip...
她就让兽医把他的拉布拉多猎狗放到水里去
and she had his Labrador put down by the vet.
没有杀那条狗
Shouldn't have killed that dog.
- 那这条狗就是导火线? - 不 电梯才是导火线
- So the dog was the last straw? - No,the lift was the last straw.
她用斧头砍他喜欢的轿车 他抓狂了 把她锁在一架电梯里
She took an ax to his favorite car,he goes mad,locks her in a lift.
自打狗那事以后 你不能怪他
You can't really blame him,after the dog.
除非他发现她是个幽闭恐怖症患者
Except he knew that she was claustrophobic.
她把他推了很远 他最后愤怒了
She pushed him so far,he eventually flipped.
为了离婚他把所有的东西给了她...
Gave her everything at the divorce settlement...
只保留了温泉疗养连锁旅馆
just kept the spa-hotel chain.
好的 告诉我关于绘画的事
All right.Tell me about the drawings.
她每周去艺术班两次 痴迷于绘画
She attends art classes twice a week.Crazy about it.
我想我要开始喜欢绘画了
I think I'm going to enjoy this.
好 你得小心点 Albie 因为她是个真正的心理高手
Yeah.Well,you be careful,Albie,because she is a real psycho bitch.
你在做什么 Eddie?
What are you doing,Eddie?
找这种《查令十字街》上提到的老式鸡尾酒
Found this old cocktail book down the Charing Cross Road.
- 天使的乳头 你要来杯吗? - 不 谢谢
- Angel's Tit.Do you want one? - No,thank you.
难以置信 纯粹娱乐的时间
Incredible.Moment of pure joy.
Albert年轻时就是玩"康格里夫"的老手
When he was younger,Albert was the doyen of the Congreve.
他能像猪嗅出块菌一样找到满怀报复心的女人
He could smell out a vengeful woman like a pig with a truffle.
好厉害的人
What a man.
失陪了
Excuse me.
- 你去哪里Ash? - 出去
- Where are you off to,Ash? - Out.
你离开是去找某个神秘女人?
You got a mystery woman stashed away?
是的 我们对她不够好 Ash?
Yeah,we're not good enough for her,Ash?
他去哪里?
Where does he keep going off to?
那是他的事
That's his business.
我想知道Albie进行得如何了
I wonder how Albie is getting on.
对不起 这是我第一次 有点紧张
Excuse me.It's my first time.I'm a little nervous.
你在和我说话?
Are you talking to me?
- 是的 我说这是我第一次 - 别紧张
- Yeah.I was saying it's my first time. - Please don't.
晚上好 大家开始吧
Good evening.Let's make a start,people.
- 丹米?欢迎来艺术班 - 谢谢
- Damien?Welcome to the class. - Thank you.
那么 如果你不介意脱掉衣服 我们就可以开始了
So,if you won't mind undressing,we'll get started.
- 什么? - 拜托
- Excuse me? - Please.
无论男女新来的都要做一次模特
The new boy or girl,they always model on their first class.
- 这是我们的一点惯例 - 好吧
- It's just our little tradition. - Okay.
丹米 你的睡袍?
Damien,your robe?
迈克
Mickey.
你还记得June吧?
You remember June,don't you?
好 谢谢
Yeah,thanks.
Mickey Stone 你看起来很吃惊
Mickey Stone.You look fabulous.
- 你也是 - 骗子
- So do you. - Liar.
怎么了 June?
What happened,June?
很多年了 头撞撞到了行驶中的车辆
Too many years head-butting moving vehicles.
她一直在治疗 直到一个月前
She was doing the flop up until a month ago.
她头上的托板移位了...
The plate in her head moved...
那太不幸了
That's too bad.
- 但是Ash在照料你? - 但却是最好的
- But Ash has been looking after you? - Only the best.
告诉他不必为我负责 打我们离婚那天起责任就终止了
Tell him I'm not his responsibility.That ended the day we divorced.
对不起 我不能那样做 June 另外 那不会是真的
Sorry,I can't do that,June.Besides,it wouldn't be true.
你也不是?
Not you,too?
你们是一家人 家人应该承担责任
You're family.And families take responsibility.
并且分担责任
And they share that responsibility.
我想告诉你 但...
I wanted to tell you,but...
- Ash? - 是的 亲爱的?
- Ash? - Yes,love?
- 他是谁? - 怎么了 他是Mickey
- Who's that man? - Why,that's Mickey.
- 你记得Mickey的 - 让他出去
- You remember Mickey. - Get him out!
没事了
It's okay.
- 我没想到会像那样 - 真的吗?
- That wasn't exactly what I expected. - Really?
我能看看吗?
May I see?
不错 我一直在寻找新会员 新眼光
It's good.I'm always looking for fresh blood,a fresh eye.
我在Knightsbridge有一间小画廊
I own a small gallery in Knightsbridge.
你认为那会给我留下印象吗?
Is that supposed to impress me?
根本不是那样 我只是想你可能...
Not at all.I just thought you might...
我是个业余爱好者 我有自知之明
I'm an amateur.I know what I am.
不是从今晚你的作品来看 事实上我不欣赏这作品
Not from looking at your work tonight.I would actually disagree.
那么你是个白痴
Then you're an idiot.
相信我 我永远不会在这些事上犯错
Believe me,I'm never wrong about these things.
也许我能带你出去喝点什么...我们能...
Perhaps I could take you out for a cup of...We could...
你知道我为什么来这个绘画班吗?
Do you know why I come to this drawing class?
我猜想是因为...
I imagine because...
这是我能把自己关上一个小时唯一能做的事
It's the one thing I do where I can lose myself for a blissful hour.
如果我想加入中老年人 去艺廊卖弄自己的技艺...
If I wanted an elderly rou?
with an art gallery hitting on me...
我宁愿去威尼斯 明白了?
I'd go to Venice.Do you understand?
- 懂了 - 好的
- Perfectly. - Good.
有些时候她还好
Some days she's fine.
然而 有时会突然降雾 她就开始困惑,烦恼
Then,suddenly,the fog will come down and she gets confused,upset.
她会好起来吗?
She will get better?
那是局部脑损伤 Mickey
It's partial brain damage,Mickey.
你一直在支撑着这个家?
And you've been paying for that home all this time?
是的 直到下周末
Yeah,until the end of next week.
那时钱就花光了
Then the money runs out.
然后会怎样?
Then what happens?
- 有些便宜点的地方 - 不行 不能让June去
- There are cheaper places. - No way.Not for June.
我记得你俩结婚的时候
I remember when you two married.
那是我们从不曾做过的事
It just wasn't something we ever did.
你和Rachel结婚了
Well,you married Rachel.
是的 我知道 但是你知道她不是我们一伙的
Yeah,I know.But she wasn't one of us,you know.
我还记得你说过:
And I remember what you said:
"仅仅是因为我们做自己所做的 并不意味着我们必须孤独"
"Just because we do what we do doesn't mean we have to be lonely."
我羡慕你可以那样说
I admired you for saying that.
你准备给他们几个说吗?
Are you going to tell the others?
她在那里会得到最好的照顾的 Ash...
She's going to get the best care there is,Ash...
那也意味着我们将需要一大笔钱
which means we're going to need a lot of money.
别烦恼了 Albert正在外面跑业务
But don't worry.Albert is out there doing the business.
我们都会好起来的
We'll be all right.
Katherine Winterborn是只超级怪物
Katherine Winterborn is an ogre of gargantuan amplitude.
你仍认为她是我们的目标?
You still think she's our mark?
她富有 她怀恨在心...
She's rich,she's bitter...
只要用对了方法 她就会像蝴蝶一样展开
and with the right key,she'll open up like a butterfly.
她有情人吗?
Any boyfriends?
不 至少我们对其一无所知
No.At least none that we know of.
那会像与尼罗河鳄鱼睡觉一样
That would be like sleeping with a Nile crocodile.
好的 那么该你出场了
Well,there's your in,then.
- 你这样想? - 我确定
- You think? - I know.
用什么 性爱?
What,sex?
等等 请等一下
Wait.Please,just a second.
June对我来说意味着很多 我证实...
June means a lot to me.I proved that...
不 不由你做 Albie
No,not you,Albie.
你那样玷污你的贞操太不值了
You're far too precious to be sullied in that way.
抱歉 把你的裤子穿好 我准备来硬的了
Sorry,put your trousers on.I'm ready and I'm bang up for it.
不 我们不会让孩子来做男人的事 对吧 Michael?
No,we don't send boys to do a man's job.Right,Michael?
不 我们不会
No,we do not.
Mickey能施展他的魅力并且不脱下裤子
Mickey can spin his charm and still keep his trousers on.
那是他伟大的天赋
It's his great gift.
你两个回温泉旅馆去 尽你们所能收集所有的信息
You two go back to the spa,get every piece of information you can.
我会安排和Katherine Winterborn见面
I'll arrange a meeting with Katherine Winterborn.
- 我找Elliot先生 - 你是Winterborn夫人?
- I'm looking for Mr.Elliot. - Mrs.Winterborn?
他让我告诉你 他在地平线休息室等你
He said to say to meet you in the Horizon Lounge.
- 楼梯在哪里? - 那可是在40层 夫人
- Where are the stairs? - It's on the 40th floor,madam.
电梯就在那边
The lifts are just through there.
- 我听说电梯中间出了问题 - 什么?
- Problem with the middle lift,I hear. - Excuse me?
我们接到责任经理报告说是左中央电梯出现颤抖
We got a report from the duty manager that the left central lift was juddering.
我没听说过 我打电话问他
News to me.Let me call him.
只需五分钟 我不能不管它
It'll take me five minutes.I can't just leave it.
我要么修理它要么关掉它 对我来说这都一样 先生
Either I fix it or I shut it down.It's all the same to me,sir.
- 去修吧 - 好的
- Go on. - All right.
Winterborn夫人
Mrs.Winterborn.
(抱歉 有个紧急会议 Andy Elliot)
抱歉
Sorry.
出什么事了?
What's happening?
有人吗?
Hello?
抱歉 先生
Sorry about this,sir.
稍等一会儿就正常了
I'll have you moving in a while.
请你快点 我开会要迟到了
Quick as you can,please.I'm late for a meeting.
难道总是这样的?
Isn't that always the way?
你还好吧?
Are you all right?
不 我非常不喜欢这样 你能催他们快点吗?
No,I don't do lifts very well.Can you hurry them,please?
注意 你能快点吗?这里面有位女士感觉不好了
Look,could you hurry it up?There's a lady in here feeling unwell.
好的 不会等太久的
Yeah,it shouldn't be too long now.
- 你在做什么? - 你很惊恐
- What are you doing? - You're panicking.
看着我 看我的眼睛 什么事都别想 什么人也别想
Now look at me.Look into my eyes.Think of nothing and no one else.
- 我要吐了 - 看着我 这里
- I'm going to be sick. - Look at me.Here.
非常好 现在 想象一下 你在河边非常地镇静
Very good.Now,think,you're very calm.You're by a river bank.
阳光照在河水的涟漪上 河水幽绿而凉爽
The sun is dappling the water.The water is dark green and very cool.
微风拨动着流水 你听到了吗?
There's a breeze playing with the rushes.Can you hear it?
好了?非常好
Yeah?Very good.
你非常镇静地坐在岸边 用你的脚激起水花
You're very calm as you sit by the bank and splash your feet in the water.
你能感觉到冰凉的河水从你脚上流过
Can you feel the cold water against your skin?
非常好
Very good.
我和责任经理谈过
I spoke to the duty manager.
这位美国商人在纽约或芝加哥
There was this American businessman in New York.Or maybe it was Chicago.
谁给你们公司打电话的?
Who called your company?
他在一架电梯里全神贯注工作了三个小时 不通风 没有空调
He got stuck in a lift for three hours.No ventilation,no air con.
最后当他们把他弄出来时 他的心脏像只易碎的包一样破了
When they finally got him out,his heart had exploded like a crisp packet.
快点弄完
Just hurry up and finish.
它很糟糕
Terrible,it was.
我们在动
We're moving.
是的 我们还好 我和你在一起
We are.We're okay.Stay with me.
现在我们要站起来 好吗?你做的很好
Now we're gonna stand up,okay?You're doing very well.
我们起来 非常镇静 吸气再呼气
Here we go.Very calm.Breathe in and out.
做的很好
That's very good.
- 你现在要好些吗? - 是的 谢谢
- You're gonna be all right now? - Yes,thank you.
我想你该给这位女士道歉
I think you owe this lady an apology.
至于我的事 如果我的钱有任何损失...
As far as I'm concerned,if I lose any money...
因为我我开会迟到了 我会把帐单寄给你的
because I'm late for this meeting,I will send you the bill.
你忘了这个
You forgot this.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 我完全应该谢谢你 - 不必客气 真的
- And I wanted to thank you properly. - There's no need,really.
我喜欢你的河流
I liked your river.
你的河流
Your river.
现在 如果你再耽搁...
Now,if you'll excuse me...
- 你开会迟到了 - 是的
- You're late for your meeting. - Yes.
我能请你吃晚饭以表谢意吗?
Can I buy you dinner tonight as a thank-you?
不胜欣喜
I'd be delighted.
Patrick Greene
Patrick Greene.
- 去开会吧 - 好的
- Now get to your meeting. - Yes.
橘汁 冰
Orange juice.Ice.
矿泉水冰块?
Mineral-water ice cubes?
注意 我给你说过多少次了...
Look,how many times do I have to tell you people...
我们再也别那样做了
we don't do that anymore.
对不起 先生 我不知道
Sorry,sir,I didn't know.
别让我再告诉你
Don't make me tell you again.
那个不好意思
Sorry about that.
你能想象那样?矿泉水冰块?
Can you imagine that?Mineral-water ice cubes?
有点极端
A bit extreme.
- 你在这里什么都好吧? - 非常好 什么都很完美
- Everything all right for you here? - Great.Everything's perfect.
- 你是经理? - 不 我是业主
- You the manager? - No,I'm the owner.
- Stephen Winterborn - Cindy Moore
- Stephen Winterborn. - Cindy Moore.
- 你的旅馆真舒适 - 谢谢
- Lovely place you've got here. - Thank you.
我是不是在某处读到过...
Didn't I read somewhere...
你将把你的产业上市发行?
you're floating your business on the stock exchange?
这个消息一定是你在金融报纸上读到的
You must read the very small print on the financial pages.
是的
I do.
是的 我们打算发行股票
Yeah,we're about to go public.
真让人兴奋
Exciting.
我希望是
I hope so.
如果你不介意我想问问你是做什么的?
What do you do,if you don't mind me asking?
我在这个城市工作
I work in the city.
- 真的?做什么的? - Stephen
- Really?Doing what? - Stephen.
- 很高兴认识你 Moore小姐 - 我也是
- Nice to meet you,Miss Moore. - Likewise.
祝你股票上市好运
Good luck with the launch.
- 你想要点什么? - 来杯马提尼
- What can I get you? - Dry martini.
- 先生? - 你的蒸馏水从哪里来的?
- Sir? - Where's your still water from?
- 英格兰 先生 - 英格兰哪里?
- England,sir. - Where in England?
- 赫里福郡 - 那很不错
- Herefordshire. - That's fine.
不要柠檬 两块矿泉水冰块
No lemon.Two mineral-water ice cubes.
对不起 先生 我们只有一般的冰块
Sorry,sir,we only have regular ice cubes.
从水里提炼出来的至少要7个人仔细检查的冰块
Made from water that has gone through at least seven human beings.
不要冰 谢谢
No ice,thank you.
- 你在香港做过什么? - 挣钱...
- What were you doing in Hong Kong? - Making money...
观测台风从哪条路线登陆 直到香港被中国收回
seeing which way the wind would blow once the Chinese took it back.
- 风往哪条路线吹? - 回到伦敦
- Which way is it blowing? - Back to London.
你呢?除了在电梯里惊慌 你还做什么?
What about you?What do you do,apart from panic in lifts?
- 你不知道我是谁? - 我应该知道?
- You don't know who I am? - Should I?
这里的其他所有人都应该知道
Every other person in here would.
我就是那个杀死前夫的狗的坏女人
I'm the evil bitch who killed her ex-husband's dog.
我读到过
I read about that.
媒体非常不喜欢你对吗?
The press didn't like you very much,did they?
给点时间我会熬过来的
I'll get over it,given time.
你现在就可以离开 我不会生气的
You can run away now.I won't be offended.
我在这里很好 尽管这有些怪异
I'm fine where I am.It's funny though.
- 你不想知道关于那条狗的事? - 如果你愿意就会告诉我
- Don't you want to know about the dog? - You'll tell me if you want to.
打搅一下 先生 你们的晚餐准备好了
Excuse me,sir.Your table's ready.
你什么时候开始在温泉旅馆工作的
When did you start at the spa?
三个月前
Three months ago.
- 你喜欢在那工作? - 还好
- Do you like it? - It's all right.
你球打的不错 很有天分
You're pretty good with these balls.You're a natural.
让我把球杆把手握稳点
Let me get just a nice firm grip on the end there.
那么是谁先给你这份工作的?
So who got you in the job in the first place?
让我把它打进去 准备好了?
Let me push it through.Ready?
- 哇 - 一起打进的
- Wow. - Together.
- 你问了许多问题 - 是吗?
- You ask a lot of questions. - Do I?
- 我能问你一个问题吗? - 好的 随便问
- Can I ask you one? - Yeah,fire away.
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
只是和你一起打台球
Just playing with balls with you.
你姐姐在哪里?
Where is your sister?
她和一些朋友在剧院
She's at the theater with some friends.
- 真不好意思 - 为什么?
- That's a shame. - Why?
她很漂亮 她可以和我们一起来的
She's pretty.She could have come with us.
- 我们去哪里? - 去我那里
- Where are we going? - To my place.
她想要的东西我给不了她 于是她找了某个能给她的人
She wanted things I couldn't give her.So she found someone who could.
- 受伤了吧? - 是的 像刀割一样
- Hurts,doesn't it? - Yeah,like a razor.
孩子如何?
Kids?
在我成为她所期待的人之前她不会要孩子
She wouldn't have them until I'd become what she wanted.
如果她求你 你还会要她回去吗?
Would you take her back if she asked?
不 我永远也给不了她想要的
No,I could never give her the things that she wants.
问题不在于此
That wasn't the question.
你说过那很怪异 什么很怪异?
You said it was funny.What's funny?
我告诉你我的私事 而你却说那很怪异
I told you about my business and you said it was funny.
- 噢 是的 一个巧合 - 告诉我
- Oh,yeah.A coincidence. - Tell me.
那是私事 我们不想谈私事
It's business.We don't want to talk business.
我喜欢谈私事
I like talking business.
我在东南部修建了一座豪华饭店
I'm setting up a luxury hotel complex in the southeast.
起先我们修建一座 但我们在五年内会修建一个较大的连锁店
We're starting with one,but we'll create a major chain within five years.
听起来你很自信 那是个很难运作的业务
You sound very confident.It's a hard business to get right.
一些在香港的英国商人准备回国...
Some British businessmen in Hong Kong are ready to come home...
而这就是他们想做的
and this is what they want to do.
每个人最低投入40万英镑
Each man has put in a minimum stake of 400,000...
而我的任务就是建起它并让它运作起来
and my job is to get it up and running.
你会成为我前夫的直接竞争对手
You'd be in direct competition with my ex-husband.
- 抱歉了 - 别那样说 我认为那很热闹
- Sorry about that. - Don't be.I think it's hilarious.
- 你还需要多少钱? - 我们用所有的方法筹集
- How much more money do you need? - We're all sorted.
- 资金充足? - 为什么关心这个?
- Fully funded? - Why?
想刺激一下你前夫?
Thinking of irritating your ex-husband?
那并不重要 是吗?
That would be petty,wouldn't it?
看来他没有给你的宝贝提供芦荟床上的服务?
So he didn't serve your heart on a bed of asparagus,huh?
不 当她意识到可以利用我报复她丈夫的时候就没那样
No,not when she realized she could use me to get back at her husband.
- 她是个有趣的女人 - 有趣?
- She's an interesting woman. - Interesting?
你们谈了些什么?
What did you talk about?
生活 爱情 前妻
Life,love,exes.
你和她谈论过Rachel?
You talked to her about Rachel?
- 你甚至不和我们谈Rachel - 她要我谈的
- You don't even talk to us about her. - She asked.
Danny在哪里?
Where's Danny?
他在搞定温泉旅馆的俄罗斯姑娘
He's working the Russian girl from the spa.
她也一定很有趣
She must be interesting,too.
- 有任何点击吗 Ash? - 不 还没有
- Any hits yet,Ash? - No,not yet.
你要走了?
You're going?
是的 我必须得走了 抱歉
Yeah,I gotta go.I'm sorry.
回你姐姐那去?
Back to your sister.
是的 你知道她会担心的
Yeah,well,you know,she does worry.
把钱放在桌子上
Leave the money on the table.
什么?
Excuse me?
200块
200.
- 你想要钱? - 当然
- You want money? - Of course.
你不会是妓女吧?
You're not a hooker,are you?
我不介意你怎么说
I don't mind what word you use.
等一下 我想你清楚我们...
Hang on a minute.I thought we were,you know...
你以为什么?
You thought what?
- 我不能花钱嫖女人 - 为何不?
- I can't pay for sex. - Why not?
因为你知道我...
Because I'm,you know...
我的意思是 你知道 那不是...我不是嫖客
I mean,you know,it's not...I'm not a payer-for-sexer.
好了 你必须付钱 如果你不付 他们会杀了我
Well,you have to.If you don't,they'll cut me.
谁会那样做?
Who will?
我为之工作的人
People I work for.
她进网站了
She's in.
- 她在浏览哪里? - 公司董事相片
- Where's she off to? - Photograph of company directors.
她喜欢你
She likes you.
我相信她上钩了
I do believe we have her.
开始第二阶段
Let's begin stage two.
那个人怎样?
Well,what about that one?
看他的鞋
Look at his shoes.
手工制造 或许是Jermyn街的 放干他的血需要太长时间
Handmade.Probably Jermyn Street.It'll take too long to bleed him dry.
我想...噢 真可爱
Well,I think...Oh,lovely.
那位如何?
What about that one?
过于漂亮了 漂亮女孩是不玩纸牌的
Too pretty.Pretty girls don't play poker.
我不相信你说的
I can't believe you said that.
你的目标来了
There's your mark.
别致的吉普赛人 手工卷制雪茄 不成对的袜子
Bohemian chic,roll-ups,odd socks.
我认为他是个存在主义者
Thinks he's an existentialist.
喜欢用木碗吃鱼
Be like shooting a fish in a bowl.
那我们一会儿见
I'll see you later then.
非常好 正是我们想找的
Great.Just what we're looking for.
我已经为经理人提供了数据
I've got the number for the managing agents.
- 你提供过了? - 是的
- Have you? - Yes.
我恨经理人 Brian
I hate managing agents,Brian.
- 是吗? - 是的
- Do you? - Yeah.
但我决定喜欢你 我非常喜欢你
But I've decided I like you.I like you very much.
大多建筑学研究者只对修建摩天大楼感兴趣...
Most architecture students are only interested in building skyscrapers...
以及为团体的贪欲而修建的纪念碑
and monuments to corporate greed.
我 打算为下层人民提供伟大的设计
Me,I'm about bringing great design to the underclass.
绝对是 他们会为之感激流涕的
Absolutely.Yeah,they're crying out for it.
- 你现在研究什么? - 我研究心理学
- What are you studying? - I'm sort of...Psychology.
那有一点庸俗
That's a bit bourgeois.
你可以那样说 但是你知道 了解你的敌人
You might say that,but,you know,know your enemy.
通过研究人类心理...
Through a study of human psychology...
我想改变 想推翻国际资本主义思潮
I want to invert,to subvert,the mind of the international capitalists.
随你笑好了 让我给你点示例
Laugh away,but let me just give you an example of that.
永远别太擅长玩牌了 我只是...
Never been very good with cards.I just...
用手夹着牌...抱歉 不太会洗牌
It's the thing you got to clip...Sorry,can't shuffle.
我要从这上面抽出五张我没看过的牌 很公平的
I'm gonna take five cards off the top here,which I haven't seen.Fair enough.
你仅仅是拿起来 握着它们 把它们放在你手上 好了?
But take them.Just hold onto them.Put them in your hand,yeah?
从我对你的了解 我要告诉你...
From my knowledge of you,I'm going to be able to tell...
只需从你的表情 看出你手中哪张最大...
just from reading your face,which is the highest card...
你曾被催眠过?
in that hand.You ever been hypnotized?
好的 看着我 看着卡片 放松
Okay,just look at me.Look at the cards,relax.
第一张最大
The first one is the highest.
有时需要点时间 别打断我 好吗?看着我
Sometimes it takes a while.Don't block me,all right?Look at me.
第三张牌最大
The third card is the highest one.
你还剩些什么?
What you got left?
有时候会有效 但我这是第一年研究
It does work sometimes,but I'm in the first year.
你很会玩牌吗?
You are pretty good with cards,aren't you?
现在 别对我撒谎 我能区别得出来 不 你很会玩
Now,don't lie to me,I can tell.No,you're good.
我们应该玩一把...叫什么名字来着?扑克
We should have a game of...What's it called?Poker.
准备好了?
Ready?
好的 我要押20块 你想押多少?
Right,I'm gonna put 20 down.How many do you want?
我押20
I got 20.
- 该我出牌了 - 翻牌
- Time for me to get out. - Check.
押20 我跟10
20.In.I'll go for 10.
20.
我出局了
I'm out.
那么你是什么牌?
So what have you got?
一张J最大
Jack high.
两对 初学者运气好
Two pairs.Must be beginner's luck.
那也意味着你欠我一大笔钱
Which also means that you owe me quite a lot of money.
兄弟 你把我输光了
You've cleaned me out,man.
那你还擅长做什么?你知道 比如当一个建筑师?
So are you any good?You know,like,being an architect?
这辈子做个最好的建筑师 看 我会把我的表抵押给你
The best in my year.Look,I'll put my watch into the mix.
我不想要你的表
I don't want your watch.
我没有其他什么东西了
I don't have anything else.
我想要的是你有的某些东西...
There must be something you have that I want...
某些你所拥有而我没有的技能
some skill that you possess that I don't.
比如什么?
Like what?
这很好 丹尼
These are good,Danny.
他不会玩牌 但他绘制的建筑图很可爱
He can't play cards,but he does draw a lovely building.
Michael
Michael.
我们得走了 表演时间到了
Here we go.Showtime.
我想见Greene先生
I'd like to see Mr.Greene,please.
你有预约吗?
Do you have an appointment?
告诉他Winterborn夫人来这里见他就行了
Just tell him Mrs.Winterborn is here to see him.
行了 Sharon 又见面了
That's quite all right,Sharon.Hello again.
这边请
Come this way.
昨天晚上我在想你
I thought about you last night.
那是个美好的夜晚吧?请随便坐
It was a good night,wasn't it?Please have a seat.
我想见见你的工地
I'd like to see your site.
- 为什么? - 个人兴趣
- What for? - Professional interest.
你要知道投资是否全部到位了?
You know it's fully invested?
我仍想看看你的工地
I'd still like to see your site.
好的
Okay.
那里会建主住宿区,餐厅,游泳池
That would be the main accommodation block there.Restaurant.Pool.
- 户外还是户内? - 一个户外一个户内...
- Outdoor or indoor? - One outdoor,one indoor...
两边都有接待室
both flanked by the treatment rooms.
是个漂亮的地方
It's a beautiful place.
陆路交通便利 到机场只需半个钟头
Good road and rail access.Airport in half an hour.
- 建筑许可? - 都搞定了
- Planning permission? - All sorted.
- 员工? - 已经开始在招聘了
- Staff? - Already started headhunting.
很难找到优秀人选
Hard to find good people.
是的 但不是不可能
Yeah,but not impossible.
你前夫已经选走了
Your ex-husband has loads.
我想看看你的建筑师
I'd like to see your architect.
- 但我们谈过这个... - 让我看看
- But we've discussed this... - Indulge me.
把它称作个人兴趣
Call it professional interest.
这边走
This way.
我记得你得到了建筑许可
I'm impressed you got planning permission.
- 那很不容易 - 走开 你们入侵了 给我出去
- It wasn't easy. - Bugger off!You're trespassing!Get off!
所有我要说的就是别缩减建筑进展
All I'd say is don't scrimp in the building and development.
说者容易做者难 开销螺旋式地...
It's easy to do,the costs spiral...
人造大理石和真大理石看起来效果一样好 但别做人造的
and the marble effect looks nearly as good as real marble.Don't do it.
并且要明确别在卧室节省开支
And definitely don't cut costs in the bedrooms.
家具设备等要比客户在家里的好 不能差
They should be better than guests have at home,not worse.Furnishings.
我要告诉你它会是至高无上的
It will be unrivaled,I give you my word.
而且开张那天你能成为我尊敬的客人
And on opening day you can be my guest of honor.
我喜欢看到他发现我加入了他的竞争对手时的表情
I'd love to see his face when he finds out I'm involved with the competition.
- 他会狂怒的 - 但是Katherine从所有权考虑...
- He will be furious. - But,Katherine,with all due respect...
你并没有加入竞争方
you're not involved with the competition.
我会在你的业务上投资10万英镑的
I'm going to invest 100,000 in your business.
你不能那样做
You can't do that.
没人比我更清楚这个了
No one knows more about this than me.
让我投资10万英镑 而且我会成为你的免费顾问
Let me invest 100,000 and I'll be your consultant for free.
- 你确信那是你想做的? - 绝对确定
- Are you sure it's what you want? - Positive.
我明天把协议带过来
I'll bring the papers over tomorrow.
- 两杯香槟 - 好的
- Two glasses of champagne,please. - Okay.
很好,都会列出来的
Okay,furnishings.
好的 你会把它直放在货车上吧?
Good.Would you put that straight in the van?
Brian 非常感谢你
Brian,thank you so much.
你是个明星 谢谢你
You're a star.Thank you for that.
抱歉我浪费了你的时间
I'm sorry I've wasted your time.
什么使你改变主意了?
What made you change your mind?
这几个月里 我醒来所想到的第一件事...
For months now,the first image in my head when I wake...
就是他和女友在笑而且是大笑...
is of him and his little girlfriend,smiling and laughing...
享受着我所创造的生活
enjoying the lifestyle I've created.
我恨他 我想让他伤心
I hate him.I want to hurt him.
Katherine 你所做的所有事...
Katherine,all you have to do...
但在我余生中不会再像那样过了
But that's no way to live the rest of my life.
沉浸于愤怒与苦楚之中
Eaten away with anger and bitterness.
那样他就又赢了
That way he wins again.
与你一起工作应该很有意思 我相信...
It would have been fun to work with you,I'm sure of that...
但那对我来说是种错误
but it would have been wrong for me.
我需要一个新的开始而那不是 很抱歉
I need a fresh start and this isn't it.I'm sorry.
- 我不能劝告你? - 我知道你甚至不会来劝
- I can't persuade you? - I know you won't even try.
我希望决定是为你自己作出的
I hope it works out for you.
谢谢 我欠你很多
Thank you.I owe you a lot.
至于那条狗 它是被一辆车撞死的...
About the dog,it was hit by a car...
它极度痛苦
and was in great distress.
兽医说应该放下它 我才那样决定的
The vet said it should be put down,and I made that decision.
所以你让她走掉了?
So you let her walk away?
我就往常一样给了她一条出路 而这次她把握住了
I gave her an out,like always.This time she took it.
重要的是你是如何极力怂恿她的?
How hard did you try and persuade her?That's the point.
许多事情会做成这样的 Michael 人们是会有所展望的
A lot of work has gone into this,Michael.People have expectations.
伟大的 Mickey Bricks失败了
The great Mickey Bricks,falling for a mark.
这是个道德问题
It's a question of ethics.
- 道德?好血腥的道德啊? - 冷静
- Ethics?What bloody ethics? - Calm down.
- 看在基督的份上 我们是在欺诈 - 我们不欺诈正直的人
- We're con men,for Christ's sake! - We do not cheat honest people.
June怎么办?
What about June?
我们会想想办法 我们一直在想办法
We'll think of something.We always do.
- 梦幻般的作爱 Ash? - 不 谢谢 Eddie
- Fancy a Slow Comfortable Screw,Ash? - No,thanks,Eddie.
喂?
Hello?
抱歉这么晚给你打电话 Winterborn夫人
Sorry to phone you so late, Mrs.Winterborn.
但恐怕接生员明天早晨不能到你那里了
But I'm afraid that the midwife won't be able to get out to you in the morning.
- 什么接生员? - 地区接生员
- What midwife?- The district midwife.
我想你一定打错电话了
I think you must have the wrong number.
Stephen Winterborn夫人 出生日期:1983年9月13日
Mrs.Stephen Winterborn. Date of birth:September 13,1983.
据我们的记录是你丈夫昨晚带你来的
Your husband brought you in yesterday, according to our records.
Winterborn先生不再在这里住了
Mr.Winterborn no longer resides at this address.
永远别再打来了
Never call this number again.
什么让你改变主意了?
What made you change your mind?
当我23岁时怀过孕
When I was 23,I got pregnant.
完全是个意外 没有计划过的
It was a complete accident,unplanned.
但当我发现时我非常高兴
But when I found out,I was so happy.
我告诉Stephen时他只是说:
I told Stephen and he just said:
"但我们说好不要孩子的"
"But we're not going to have children.We agreed."
他是对的
And he was right.
我们都认为事业应该在第一位的
We agreed the business would come first.
但我没高兴的感觉
But I couldn't help feeling elated.
发生了什么?
What happened?
我们谈过 他决定...
We talked about it.He decided...
他威逼我直到我流产
He bullied me until I had an abortion.
他就是那样对我的
And that was that for me.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
现在我听说他让他的小妓女怀孕了
Now I hear he's got his little tart pregnant.
我将投资10万给你...
I'll give you 100,000 worth of investment...
而你要给我在温泉旅馆完全的行动自由
and you give me free rein over the spa.
我会让它焕发光彩的
I'll make it sparkle.
你怎么发现她怀孕的?
How did you find out she was pregnant?
我接到一个医院打错的电话
I got a call by mistake from the hospital.
什么时候?
What time was this?
昨天深夜
Late last night.
别走
Don't go.
我得走了
I have to.
我还没有签合同
I haven't signed the contract.
你不需要签了
And you're not going to.
你是什么意思 Patrick?
What do you mean,Patrick?
这样做对你来说是不好的
It's just not the right thing for you to do.
我不明白
I don't understand.
相信我
Trust me on this.
我们什么时候再见?
When am I going to see you again?
Katherine 你再也不会见到我了
Katherine,you're never going to see me again.
为什么?
Why?
必须得这样
That's just the way it has to be.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们这样结束了?
You're done with me,are you?
愚笨 痛苦的女人 容易勾搭有利可图?
Stupid,bitter woman,good for a shag and a few quid?
这里没有旅馆 Katherine 没有温泉 没有投资者
There is no hotel,Katherine.No spa,no investors.
我也不叫Patrick
My name is not Patrick.
我和我的同谋把你选中作可能的欺诈对象
Some associates and myself picked you out as a potential victim.
你富有,愤怒,困惑,怀恨在心
You were rich,bitter,angry,obsessed.
对你下手的时机已经成熟了
You were ripe to be plucked.
你是骗子
You're a con man.
但我不会让你成为我们的目标 我不会那样做
But I will not let you be our mark.I won't be a part of it.
等等
Wait.
你在骗我
You were setting me up.
是的
I was.
你们是为了诈骗钱财 你是那样说的?
You con people for money,that's what you're saying?
你们都是一样的 你们都一样
You're all the same,all of you.
20万英镑
200,000.
- 我会给你20万英镑 - 没有温泉旅馆
- I'll give you 200,000. - There is no spa.
谁在跟你说温泉了?我要你去把我前夫整垮
Who said anything about a spa?I want you to destroy my ex-husband.
狗咬狗
A rat to catch a rat.
- 别这样做 - 你出价多少 卑鄙的家伙 25万?
- Don't do this. - 250,000.What's your price,scumbag?
我想看着他蒙羞
I want to see him humiliated.
不 我们做那样做的
No,it's not what we do.
我们只骗下流的人
It's one thing conning a nasty piece of work.
她是个下流的家伙
She is a nasty piece of work.
为了报酬而破坏一个人的生活是完全不一样的
It's quite another destroying a man's life for a fee.
她想整垮的那个家伙又如何?
What's this bloke like she wants to destroy?
- 他还不错 有点自大 但... - 实际上 他并不让人满意
- He's all right.A bit full of himself,but... - No,he's not pleasant,actually.
迫使她流产...
Forced her to have an abortion...
跟着一个年轻模特跑了 并且很快地让她怀孕
ran off with a younger model,and promptly got her pregnant.
- 你甚至没有见过他 - 我了解他这种人
- You haven't even met him. - I know his type.
我们为什么在谈论他?
Then why are we talking about it?
如果他那样坏 听起来他跟其他骗子没什么区别
If he's that bad,he doesn't sound any different from any other con.
而且还要考虑June的事
And there's June to think about.
不 她不想我们为她做什么
No,she wouldn't want us to do anything just because of her.
尽管如此我会做的
I would,though.
好吧 那么我们要快点行动起来
Okay,then we have to move fast.
还有两天他就要把产业发行上市了
He's floating his business in two days.
- 那时我们要搞定他 - 弱点是什么?
- That's when we get him. - What's the in?
我不知道 他是个对所有帐目都非常谨慎的人
I have no idea.He's a very careful man,by all accounts.
- 女人? - 他有过两个女人
- Women? - He's had two in his whole life.
报复
Revenge.
如果我们让他知道他妻子设法让他破产...
If we let him know his wife is setting him up for a fall...
我们可能用那种方式引他上钩
we might hook him in that way.
- 我不想把她卷进来 - 血腥的地狱 Mickey
- I don't want her involved. - Bloody hell,Mickey.
一定还有些破绽 他内部的破绽
There must be something.A hole in his wall.
我们没有太多时间来调查
We don't have very long to find it.
你不能小声点吗?
You wanna keep your voice down?
伟大的Danny Blue花钱嫖俄罗斯妓女
The great Danny Blue paid for it with a Russian hooker.
- 用了多少钱 Danny? - 你就不能闭嘴吗?
- How much was it,Danny? - Can you please just shut up?
那足够了吗?
Is it enough?
他的温泉旅馆里面在卖淫?
A prostitution racket being run from his hotel spa?
那就能搞定他
Lt'll crucify him.
- 那现在该怎么做? - 我们需要证据
- So what do we do now? - We need proof.
不 不行
No.No way.
得了 你做过一次了 有什么区别呢?
Come on,you did it once.What's the difference?
我那时不知道她是个妓女
I didn't know she was a hooker then,did I?
我得为名誉着想
I've got a reputation to think of.
人终归一死的 Danny
Every silver cane has a grubby end,Danny.
- 而且在必须的时候... - 你该献身了 Danny男孩
- And when needs must... - You grab the grubby end,Danny boy.
- 不 - Danny 我们需要你
- No. - Danny,we need you.
如果你不能从这个女人那里得到些具体的...
If you can't get something concrete from this woman...
整个计划就会失败
this whole thing falls down.
好吧
All right.
但我先说好 听好 没人知道这次的任何事
But,I mean it,listen,no one is to know anything about this.
谢谢你 Danny
Cheers,Danny.
Eddie Danny嫖妓了
Eddie,Danny pays for sex.
出租车
Taxi!
你好
Hello!
我是Stephen Winterborn 我们在我的一家温泉旅馆见过
Stephen Winterborn.We met at one of my spas.
是的 你好 当然
Oh,yeah.Hi.Of course.
那个讨厌矿泉水冰块的人
The man who hates mineral-water ice cubes.
- 你去哪里? - 回城去
- Which way are you heading? - Back to the city.
我也是 我们要合坐一辆出租吗?
Me,too.Shall we share the cab?
好的
Yeah,okay.
你没告诉过我你在这座城市干什么
You never told me what you did in the city.
- 你从没问过 - 实际上我问过
- You never asked. - I did,actually.
我是新股观测员 为我的客户提供投资参考
I monitor new flotations.Advise my board whether they should invest in them or not.
你会怎样向你的客户评价我
What would you advise your board about me?
我真还不知道
I don't know,really.
我一般追踪比盘点比你大的一些股
I normally follow much bigger flotations than yours.
- 没冒犯的意思 - 我不介意
- No offense. - None taken.
那么你在哪里吃午饭?去Docklands的一家可爱小店?
So where are you having the launch?Went to a lovely one at the Docklands.
在温泉旅馆
At the spa.
- 很好 - 你认为我应该做的更多一些?
- Nice. - You think I should have done more?
最重要的事在于展示
The most important thing is the presentation.
我用一般公共关系把某些公司拖垮
I got my usual PR firm to knock something up.
"把某些公司拖垮?"
"Knock something up"?
Stephen 这是你商业生涯最重要的时刻
Stephen,this is the most important moment of your business life.
我有位朋友我想你应该见见
I've got a friend I think you should meet.
他们提前来了
They're early.
这个人没什么特别的
The man is nothing short of astonishing.
Cindy 你在这里做什么?
Cindy,what on earth are you doing here?
我想让你见见我朋友
I want you to meet my friend.
久仰大名 Cavendish先生
I've heard great things about you,Mr.Cavendish.
我在工作
I'm working.
抱歉 他是个很有才华的公共关系专家 但却非常粗鲁
Sorry.He's a brilliant PR,but very rude.
你想让你看看Stephen的展示
I want you to have a look at Stephen's presentation.
为什么我要那样做?
Now why would I want to do that?
因为我非常和蔼地请你帮忙
Because I'm asking you nicely.
...体验纵情享受...
...experience,which pampers and relaxes...
同时精神振奋恢复活力
while at the same time, refreshes and energizes.
我们的每家温泉旅店提供一种独特的体验
Each of our spas offers a unique experience.
但所有的旅店都有一个共同点 即是放纵你的心情
But the one thing they have in common is indulgence.
Winterborns连锁温泉旅馆
Winterborns Hotel and Spas.
- 你认为如何? - 非常不错
- What do you think? - Very nice.
使我想起你在介绍片里面的广告
Reminds me of those ads you have in provincial cinemas.
"泰姬陵印度餐厅是这介绍片的缩影"
"The Taj Mahal Indian Restaurant,just moments from this cinema."
Cavendish先生 你难道没有点兴奋吗?
Mr.Cavendish,can't you just fizz it up a bit?
不 我没兴奋
No,I don't do fizz.
拜托了 Cavendish先生 我会让它值得你帮忙的
Come on,Mr.Cavendish.I'll make it worth your while.
怎么了?
So,what's up?
张开点
Open it.
另外还有多少女孩会干这行当?
So how many of the other girls are turning tricks?
只有俄罗斯和立陶宛姑娘
Only the Russian ones,and the Lithuanians.
还有乌克兰姑娘
And the Ukrainian girl.
如果经理发现了会怎样?
What would the management do if they found out?
他们和组织者是一伙的
They're the ones who organized it.
你确定?
You sure about that?
莫斯科黑手党的人告诉我在英格兰有个工作的机会...
The Mafia guy in Moscow told me there is a job opportunity in England...
- 于是我欣然接受了 - 黑手党?
- and I jumped at it. - The Mafia?
那旅馆经理从你们这些姑娘身上榨取大笔的钱
So the management of the hotel are making a lot of money out of you girls.
我们一周至少得为三位客人提供服务
We have to service at least three clients a week.
服务?
Service?
- 紧张了? - 有点
- Nervous? - A bit.
别紧张 这都还应付得来
Don't be.It's all under control.
听说今年对你很重要
And I hear it's a big year for you.
你和Charlotte快要有小孩了
You and Charlotte.The pitter-patter of tiny feet.
- 谁告诉你的? - 小道消息
- Who told you that? - I heard it on the grapevine.
肯定不可信 我不能生育的 失陪一下
It's highly unlikely.I've never been able to have children.Excuse me.
看在上帝的份上 再小心一点
For God's sake,be more bloody careful.
可爱的执行之夜
Lovely night for an execution.
- 确定要做了? - 他是个杂种
- No doubts? - He's a bastard.
这就是你如何对付杂种的问题了
This is how you deal with bastards.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen.
你们好 打搅一下
Hello.Excuse me.
你们好 感谢你们出席晚会
Hi.Thank you all for coming.
今晚是我人生中最自豪的夜晚...
Tonight is the proudest night of my life...
被朋友们包围着 尊敬的客人们以及我所爱的女人
to be surrounded by friends,honored guests,and the woman I love.
许多人做了许多努力才有了我们今晚之所在
It's taken a lot of people a lot of work to get where we are tonight.
我发自心底地想感谢他们所有的人
I want to thank them all from the bottom of my heart.
非常感谢你们 感谢你们每个人
Thank you very much,everybody.
而今晚只是一个开始 豪华之旅的第一步
But tonight is just a start,the first step on a magnificent journey.
现在放一个简短的展示片 请欣赏
And now a short presentation.Enjoy.
Winterborns温泉旅馆 让你远离日常生活
Winterborns Hotel and Spas, a retreat away from daily life.
- 有些事不太对劲儿 - 什么事?
- Something doesn't smell right. - What is it?
Stephen说他不能生育
Stephen said that he can't have children.
- 不 他让她流产的 - 我知道 有人在说谎
- No,he told her to have an abortion. - I know.Somebody's lying.
哪位?说吧 等一下 我听不清
Who?Yeah,speaking.Wait,I can't hear you.
我要...
Yeah,I'm just gonna...
Bloke从办公室打来的 他说你弄丢的耳环找到了
Bloke from the office says he found the earring you lost.
- 但是我没有弄丢过耳环 - 她没有弄丢过耳环
- But I haven't lost an earring. - She hasn't lost an earring.
哪一位?
Which one?
她不是个好女士 是个下流的女人
It's not the nice lady.It's the nasty lady.
好的 谢谢
Okay,thank you.
她回去找过耳环
She went back to find the earring.
我早些时候来过
I was here earlier.
至少我认为我来过
Well,at least I think I was.
我弄丢了一只耳环
I dropped an earring.
- 这里没人了 - 人都去哪里了?
- There's nobody here. - Where is everyone?
他们只在这里呆一天 尽管如此他们都是好人
They were only here for a day.Nice people,though.
她已经知道我们是什么人了
She's known who we are all along.
你就是这样处理这杂种的
This is how you deal with bastards.
我们漂亮的治疗师都是经过特别训练的
Our beauty therapists are specially trained.
她们来自前苏联各个地方
From all corners of the former Soviet Union,they come to work...
到这里来做妓女
to work as prostitutes.
莫斯科的黑手党给我说英格兰有个工作机会...
The Mafia guy in Moscow told me there was a job opportunity in England...
我便欣然前往
and I jumped at it.
他们惧怕暴力惩罚而不敢说出来
They cannot speak out without fear of violence and punishment.
Winterborns宣传...
Winterborns,where exploitation...
- Ash 停下来 - 太晚了 我停不了
- Ash,stop it. - It's too late.I can't.
我们在毁灭一个清白的人
We're destroying an innocent man.
看在基督的份上 你能把展示片停下来吗?
For Christ's sake,will you stop the presentation?
我对那个毫不知情
I don't know anything about that.
我会尽我所能来解释这事的
I'll try and explain this as well as I can.
看看这西装
Watch the suit.
这些都是假的 我对此毫不知情
None of this is true.I know nothing about this.
失陪
Excuse me.
你怎能这样对我?为什么?
How could you do this to me?Why?
可爱的执行之夜
Lovely night for an execution.
我向你们大家道歉
I owe you all an apology.
我放松了警惕 就被算计了
I let my guard down,and I got caught.
骗子被骗了
And the con man got conned.
永远别让目标披着你的羊皮
Never let a mark get under your skin.
我知道 对不起
I know,and I'm sorry.
我答应你们这种事再也不会发生了
I promise you all it will never happen again.
无论如何 25万英镑怎么样?
Anyway,what about the 250,000?
全在我们帐上了 每一分都在
It's in our account,every penny.
- 你告诉过June没有? - 是的
- Have you told June? - Yeah.
- Mickey 我只是想... - 不 Ash 她是是家人
- Mickey,I just want to... - No,Ash.She's family.
我和友好的DI代理谈过...
I spoke to my friendly DI in Vice...
告诉她Stephen Winterborn不知道卖淫的事
told her Stephen Winterborn knew nothing about the prostitution racket.
那至少他不会被指控
So at least he won't be charged.
谢谢你 Stacie
Thanks,Stacie.
但他们会指控Winterborn夫人在温泉旅馆外开妓院
But they'll charge Mickey's woman for running a brothel out of the spa.
是的 如果他们找到她
Yeah,if they can find her.
她把帐户清空然后离开这个国家了
She's emptied her accounts and left the country.
女人
What a woman.
她真把你给愚弄了吧?
She really had you fooled,didn't she?
- 好的 我判断错误了 - 是的 我错了
- Okay,I made an error of judgment. - Yes,you did.
"无论你说什么
"Say what you will,'tis better to be left
离开总比没爱过好"
"Than never to have loved"
威廉・康格里夫 剧作家
William Congreve,playwright.
噢 不
Oh,no.
- 这是什么 Eddie? - 康格里夫
- What is this,Eddie? - The Congreve.
用许多苦料调成的
It's made with a lot of bitters.
尝尝?苦味药 苦味女人
Get it?Bitters.Bitter women.
我建议我们干了
I'd like to propose a toast.
- 为了生活与学习 - 为了爱上目标
- To living and learning. - To falling in love with marks.
至少他不必付钱 Danny
At least he didn't have to pay,Danny.
为何干杯 Ash?
What's the toast,Ash?
为家人
To family.
味道真难喝
That's disgusting.